adslink.pw 2017-11-25

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**   
We may use the collected Personally Identifiable Information and non-personal information for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to those detailed below:   
\- We may share information We collect with affiliated companies, including our parent company and other subsidiaries of our parent company, for use in their ad serving and marketing programs. This Privacy Policy does not apply to affiliated companies and their collection, use and sharing of information.  
\- We may share your information with various third party vendors that are not part of the Company.  
\- When you participate in an in our Programs, we will transfer the information you submitted on the form to the applicable advertisers with whom we cooperate.  
\- We may use third party ad networks or ad serving companies to serve advertisements on our websites. We pass information about you to these companies so that they can deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of interest to you.  
\- We may use third party service providers to enhance our database with additional elements of our services.   
Other than as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise specifically communicated to you by Company, Company does not provide information supplied by users to any third parties, except where law, court order, or governmental authority requires or based upon the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary including, without limitation, to protect the rights of Company when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or causing harm to third parties.
